- 表演时间到 - 我刚跟希亚拍完《蜜汁男孩2》
- Showtime. - I just shot Honey Boy 2 with Shia.
闻起来像阿贝克隆比零售店 被711便利店给上了
Smells like an Abercrombie got fucked by a 7-Eleven.
- 那是牛奶吗  - 爽死了
- Is that milk? -  Heavens to Betsy!
- 那就加入吧 乐趣多多哦 - 我可是跟加里布塞玩过三人行的
- You can join the fun. - And I've had a threesome with Gary Busey.
（前情提要）
You left us for dead,
扔下我们 见死不救 现在居然装作什么都没发生过
and now it's like nothing happened?
我会杀了你
I'll fucking kill you.
- 来啊 开枪啊 - 去他妈的布彻尔
- Go on. Do it. - Fuck Butcher.
- 去他妈的休伊 - 你只会把我们全部人拖下水
- Fuck Hughie. - You're just gonna drag us all down with you.
- 妈妈 你好 - 安妮
- Mom! Annie. - Hi.
你让沃特给我注射药物的时候 我几岁
How old was I when you let Vought pump me full of drugs?
他们承诺 你将有机会过上非凡的人生
They promised that you'd have a chance at an extraordinary life.
你告诉我爸爸离开 是因为他亏掉了我们所有的积蓄
You told me that Daddy left because he lost all of our savings.
真的是因为投资失败吗
Was it really bad investments?
你的猛男秀都是装样子的
Your whole Marlboro Man act, it's fucking crap, and I--
和谐堡是一家陆军医院 沃特就是在那里试验一代五号的
Fort Harmony was an Army hospital where Frederick Vought was testing the V1.
如果还有剩下的药剂 那就一定要去那里找
If there's any more left out there, that would be the fucking place to look.
一代五号的药力强上十倍
V1's ten times more potent than today's formula.
只在早期的几个超人类身上起了效
Only worked on a handful of early Supes:
你和风暴
you and Stormfront.
- 谁是风暴  - 沃特博士的妻子 叫克拉拉
-  Who is Stormfront? -  Dr. Vought's wife Clara.
我想你是认识自由女的吧
I think you knew her as Liberty?
我们仍要去对付祖国人 对吗
We're still gonna go after Homelander, right?
没有病毒怎么去
Not without the virus.
你说我足够强大
You said I was strong enough.
你说只有我才能阻止他
You said I was the only one who could stop him.
我那样说好让你叫他离开沃特塔
I just said that so you'd get him out of the tower.
我的乖孩子
My sweet, sweet boy.
祖国人
Homelander?
鞭…炮
Fire... cracker.
有股什么味儿
What's that smell?
可能是我新的香水产品线
Oh, it, uh, might be my new perfume line.
叫“李将军的秘密”
It's General Lee's Secret.
不是
No.
是我父亲 士兵男孩
That's my father. It's Soldier Boy.
- 我闻得出 你浑身都是他的气味 - 对
- Uh, I can smell him all over you. - Right.
当然是这样 因为我们刚刚在为采访做准备
Of course. 'Cause we was just, uh, prepping for our interview.
准备
Prepping?
这个嘛…我需要你做件事
Uh... I need you for something.
是吗
You do?
我得到了最绝妙的信息
I have received the most wonderful message.
一个天使…下凡来找我
I was visited... by an angel.
她预言了我的命运
And she foretold my destiny.
那么 赞美我主 您的命运是什么呢
Wow. Well, praise be. And what is it?
神
God.
先生 那太棒了
Sir, that is wonderful.
侍奉我主是最崇高的使命了
There is no higher calling than serving the Lord.
不 不是“侍奉我主”
No. Not serving the Lord.
而是成为主
Being the Lord.
我就是弥赛亚
I am the Messiah.
我就是救世主
I'm the savior of the world.
弥…赛亚
The... Messiah?
对
Yes.
祝贺您
Congrats.
谢谢
Thank you.
我一直都知道自己很特别 我就知道
I always knew I was special. I knew it.
我受过苦 我品尝过艰难困苦
I suffered. I suffered so many hardships, and I...
而我…不明白为什么
I couldn't understand why.
但你…你
But you... you...
你一直都心知肚明…不是吗
you always saw it. Didn't you?
你一直都知道我很特别
You knew all along I was special.
所以我才选择让你
That is why I have chosen you
来传扬我即将成为真神的消息
to spread the word of my coming.
怎么传扬
How?
我们控制着地球上最强大的媒体机构
Well, we control the most powerful media apparatus on Earth.
我们的宣传 耶稣也望尘莫及
Jesus would kill for our marketing. Mm.
你觉得如何
What do you say?
您知道的 我会为您做任何事 先生
Well, you know I would do anything for you, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
《英雄克星》
第五季第四集
本WEB版外挂字幕由  风吹来的那片云  双语合并
他醒了 起死回生了
Oh, here he is. Back from the dead.
慢点 慢慢来
Easy does it. Easy.
给
Here.
有点像《星球大战5：帝国反击战》 不是吗
It's a bit like that Empire Strikes Back film, innit?
- 没看过那部 - 什么
- Uh, never saw it. - What?
- 胡说 我给你看过 - 没有
- Bollocks. I showed it to you. - No.
你给我看过《星球大战》 可妈妈一集也不让我看
You showed me Star Wars. And Mom never let me watch any of 'em.
里面有 演《意外的人生》那家伙 对吗
They're with that guy from Regarding Henry, right?
是的
Yeah.
总之 电影里有这么一幕
Anyway, there's this bit, see.
年轻的卢克跳进自己的飞船
Young Luke hops in his spaceship,
去找自己的老爸达斯维德理论
fucks off to a barney with his old man Darth Vader.
- 他收到了… - 等等
- Cops-- - Wait.
达斯维德是天行者卢克的爸爸
Darth Vader's Luke Skywalker's dad?
对 有点透露剧情了 不过 听着
Yeah. It's a bit of a spoiler. But, anyway, listen,
重点是你应该 等我们解决了病毒的问题再去
the point is you should've waited till we got the virus sorted.
这是战争
This is a war.
而你是我们最强大的武器
And you're the best weapon we got.
可要是害自己进了运尸袋 你就对谁都没有用处了
But you ain't no use to anyone if you go put yourself into a body bag
你得先把祖国人弄进运尸袋才行
fore we put Homelander in one.
至少我有足够的胆量去尝试
At least I was brave enough to try.
孩子 勇敢和愚蠢之间只有一线之隔
Well, there's a fine line between bravery and stupidity, son.
你才他妈的不在乎我
You don't give a shit about me.
也许你从来都没在乎过我
Maybe you never did.
我去再给你拿点水来
Here. I'll fetch you some more water.
该死的青少年
Fucking teenagers.
欢迎回来 牛人
Welcome back, motherfucker.
谢谢
Thank you.
刚才是怎么回事
What was that about?
没什么啊
Nothing.
有型有款嘛
Check you out.
- 谢谢 - 好了
- Thank you, thank you. -  All right.
要是你们这群傻蛋搞完“时装周”了
If you twats are all done with Fashion Week,
那就开工吧 好吧
let's get to work, yeah?
法兰奇 我们需要多久 准备出足够的病毒
Frenchie, how long till we got a dose big enough?
剩下的病毒很少 需要时间繁殖
No, there was so little virus left. It needs time to multiply.
你知道他们都是怎么说的吧  小火慢炖
You know what they say, huh? Cook low and slow.
要他妈的多久
How fucking long?
- 至少几周 - 好吧
- Weeks, at least. - Okay,
那我们现在就应该去和谐堡
then we should go to Fort Harmony now.
那里80年前就被关闭了
That place got shut down 80 years ago.
如果那里有剩余的一代五号 也不会很容易就找到
If there's any V1 left in there, it ain't gonna be easy to find.
还有个“小”问题 那里可能 会有被五号感染的畜生
And there is also the small matter of the likely V'ed-up beast
让那些童子军的内脏溢了出来 就像吉百利奶油夹心蛋
that spilled those Boy Scouts' innards like a Cadbury à la crème, huh?
我需要提醒你们 斯坦埃德加在祖国人手上吗
Do I need to remind you guys that Homelander has Stan Edgar?
很可能他们早已做好了充分的准备
Odds are they're ten steps ahead.
如果我们先得到一代五号 就能救安妮 救喜美子
If we get the V1 first, we save Annie, we save Kimiko,
救你 如果你在乎的话
we save you. If you give a shit.
要是祖国人得到了 他就会长生不老
If Homelander gets it, he's immortal,
病毒就没用了 我们就惨了
virus is useless, and we're fucked sideways.
所以 谁想去…克利尔菲尔德
So, who wants to go to... Clearfield?
谁来照顾莱恩
Who's gonna take care of Ryan?
他走了 没打招呼就走了
He's gone. He legged it.
不知道是谁的错呢
Wonder whose fault that is.
伙计 要是我的话 就不会胡乱指责
Well, I wouldn't be throwing stones if I were you, mate.
除非你能告诉我们星光在哪里
Unless you can tell us where Starlight is.
好吧 我们赶快行动吧
Right. Let's get cracking.
安妮
Annie.
爸
Dad.
听着 我得跟你谈谈
Hey, listen, I need to talk to you.
我洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
好吧 你能别扫雪了吗
Okay, can you please stop doing that?
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
我已经找了好几个月了 你很擅长躲藏
I've been looking for months. You are really good at hiding.
已经20年不见了
It has been 20 years,
可你跟我说的第一件事居然是这个
and that's the first thing that you have to say to me?
我应该说什么呢
What should I say?
爸
Dad?
安妮 这是你弟弟…梅森
Annie, this is your brother... Mason.
很简单 总统先生 您取消对公立学校的资助
It's simple, Mr. President. You defund the public schools
将款项付给祖国人自由学院
and give vouchers for the Homelander Freedom Academies.
您不想让孩子们读到同性恋企鹅
You don't want kids reading about gay penguins
或者变成觉醒的圣战分子 对吧
and becoming woke jihadis, do you?
谢谢您 先生
Thank you, sir.
我说清楚 我不吃“召你前去”这套
Let me be clear. Nobody summons me.
上次指挥我的黑人女性还是内尔卡特
The last time I let a Black woman boss me around, it was Nell Carter.
我戴着阴茎环 准备了一浴缸的科瑞起酥油
With a cock ring and a tub of Crisco.
业务分析师警告说 协议里有一项会影响你获得电影签约
B.A. flagged a deal point for your movie.
我们不能给你的拖车提供… “一大碗可卡因”
We cannot furnish your trailer with, quote, "a big bowl of cocaine."
我的附加条款里都写了
It's in my rider.
那些条款是1984年签的
From 1984.
我以为自己可以为所欲为
I think I can have whatever the fuck I want.
尽管去找祖国人谈
You're welcome to take it up with Homelander.
等他从和谐堡回来 你就可以去
When he gets back from Fort Harmony.
和谐堡
Fort Harmony?
祖国人和斯坦埃德加 进行了一番坦诚的对话
Homelander and Stan Edgar had a good heart-to-heart,
我们认为 很有可能在和谐堡找到一代五号
and we think there's a strong chance of finding V1 at Fort Harmony.
沃特博士不就是在那里 给你们进行首批注射的吗
Isn't that where Dr. Vought first injected you?
这是好消息
It's great news.
如果祖国人找到了它 就会对病毒免疫 跟你一样长生不老
If he finds it, Homelander will be immune to the virus and immortal, like you.
你们就会永远相伴 永远都是…父子
You'll get to spend eternity together. Father and son. Forever.
- 他什么时候离开的  - 还没离开呢
- When did he leave? - Hasn't left yet.
也许你可以跟他一起去 告诉他去哪里找
Maybe you could go with him, show him where to look.
毕竟 有谁比你更了解那个地方呢
After all, who knows that place better than you?
很奇怪 没有鸟或动物
It's weird. No birds or animals.
- 好像… - 地狱
- It's like-- -  Fucking hell.
你就非要把车停得那么远 是吧
Had to park on the other side of the state, didn't you?
要是走不了远路 为什么不系好靴子 混蛋
Well, if the hike's too hard, why don't you try tying your boots, motherfucker.
干她娘的
Oh, fuck that.
她娘不是我喜欢的类型 小子
Not really my type, son.
- 放尊重点好吧  - 布彻尔 知道吧 休伊说得对
- Hey, how about showing a little respect? - You know, Hughie's right, Butcher.
你应该先带她出去吃晚饭
You should take her out to dinner first.
看看
Ah, let's see here.
根据腐烂的情况 尸体暴露在这里有些时日了
Based on the decomp, these bodies have been here a while.
有什么东西将他们弄得支离破碎
Something ripped them apart.
不管是什么杀掉了那些童子军 很可能还在这片树林里隐伏跟踪
Whatever killed those Boy Scouts might still stalk these woods.
那我们走吧
Let's get a move on, then.
我们来这可不是要被大脚怪杀掉的
Didn't come out here to get bummed by Bigfoot.
天哪 真好吃
Goddamn. This is delicious.
我怎么等了这么久才尝  我之前在担心什么
Why'd I wait so long to try this? What was I worried about?
将生命献给我 也许是一条鱼的最高荣誉
Probably the highest honor a fish can have, giving their lives to me.
我敢打赌它们跟47条 处女金枪鱼一起进了鱼的天堂
I bet they go to little fish heaven, with 47 virgin tuna.
喂 搞什么 兄弟
Yo. What the fuck, bro?
- 我信任你来着 - 所以你现在会讲话了
- I trusted you. - Oh, so now you can talk, huh?
你以为使用方法派演技很容易吗
You think going full method is easy?
你知道不说话有多难吗
Do you know how hard it's been to not talk?
我最强有力的表演手段 可我却不能使用
My most powerful instrument, and I can't even use it.
不过 我十分投入 我为这个角色奉献了一切
But I fucking committed. I have given everything to this role,
而你却毫不顾忌地坑害我
and you straight up fucked me over.
等等 你还在 因为抓来斯坦埃德加而生我的气吗
Wait, are you still butthurt about me bringing in Stan Edgar?
我还以为我们是朋友
I thought we were friends.
每次人们嘲笑你有多蠢 你的超能力是个笑话
I had your back every time people laughed at how stupid you are,
你有多傻
how your powers are a joke,
需要法庭指定的守卫时 我都支持你来着
how you're so dumb you need a court-appointed guardian.
- 没人说这种话 - 很多人都在说 总说
- Nobody says that. - Yes, they do. All the time.
我们别把这事 搞成联邦案件 黑人小子
Well, let's not make a federal case out of this, Bro V. Wade.
我需要得到祖国人的赏识 抓埃德加帮我得到了
I needed a win from Homelander. Edgar was it.
这就是个狗狗的世界
It's a doggy dog world.
你想说的是狗咬狗吧
Is that what you think the phrase is?
无所谓 快把你的面具戴上吧
Whatever. Just... put your fucking mask back on.
所以就是这样了
Oh. So that's how it is, huh?
你最好小心着点
You better watch your fucking back.
是吗 你要怎样报复呢
Oh, yeah? What are you gonna do about it?
看见我抓到埃德加 祖国人很高兴 他现在很器重我
Homelander's stoked about Edgar. He loves me right now.
会延续多久
How long is that gonna last?
你真的觉得对他来说 你比他亲爸还重要
You really think you're more important to him than his own father?
我要把你的屁眼儿全撑开
Open your asshole wider.
天哪 我从后面看 这景象太疯狂了
Oh, man. The view from back here was crazy.
你喜欢
You love it.
亲爱的
Hon.
你的超人类尖叫
Your super scream.
我们得给你弄一个更结实的堵嘴球
We really got to get you a stronger ball gag.
你惩罚我罪恶小穴的方法那么狠
The way you punish my sin pit,
什么堵嘴球都不够结实
ain't no ball gag in the world strong enough.
我得说 智者姐妹说 我应该嫁给你以取悦公众的时候
I got to say, when Sage said I should marry you for the optics,
我没等她说完就把电话挂了
I hung up on her.
但我真的很喜欢精液
But I do love busting gushers...
强有力地射在你那可悲的臭脸上
...all over your pathetic worm face.
亲爱的
Aw, baby.
该死
Oh, shoot.
我得走了 我忘了要跟敬拜团队开会
I got to run. I forgot I have a-a meeting with the Worship Team.
他在说谎 教会破产了
He's lying. The church is bankrupt.
- 等等 什么 教会破产了  - 什么
- Wait, what? The church is bankrupt? - What?
谁…后背艾诗丽告诉你的吗
Who... Did Back Ashley tell you that?
亏我还对她暗送秋波呢
After all that hot eye contact I was giving her?
- 这个吃里扒外的婊子 - 这种大型教会怎么会赔钱
- That two-faced bitch. - How do you lose money on a megachurch?
你们的收入有上亿美元 并且不交税
You bring in hundreds of millions and don't pay taxes.
来教会的人减少 捐款在下降
Attendance is down. Donations are drying up.
我很确定那两架湾流飞机开销巨大
And I'm sure the two Gulfstreams don't help.
- 亏空有多少  - 就…
- How deep in the hole are you? - Just, uh...
- 一点五个亿 - 天哪 你在开玩笑吗
- 150 million. - Jesus Christ. Are you kidding me?
你本应该帮我得到12个百分点的增长 加上福音派的教众
You were supposed to get me a 12-point bump with evangelicals,
而不是让我参加国会的传讯
not hauled before Congress.
刚才你不还说喜欢 精液强有力地射在我的脸上吗
What happened to how much you love busting gushers on my face?
那是在你把我害得身败名裂之前
That was before you turned me into Tammy fucking Faye.
这种情况会招来道德委员会 传票
This is ethics committees, subpoenas.
克里斯海耶斯将会采取行动
Chris Hayes is gonna have a field day.
那我们怎么办
Well, what are we gonna do?
“我们” 不如你告诉我好了
We? You tell me.
你他妈的是上帝的使者嘛
You're the fucking emissary of God.
女士 您有访客
Ma'am, you have a visitor.
我需要你们帮我个忙
I need y'all's help with something.
天哪 闻起来像做华夫饼的面糊
Dang. Smells like a wet shit in a Waffle House in here.
看见祖国人那个傻屌了吗
Any sign of super cunt?
可能已经进去了
Could already be inside.
那…我们就去看看吧
Well, let's find out.
怎么了
What's wrong?
安妮
Annie.
她会回来的
She'll come back.
不 我都差点没命了
No. I almost died.
但她想的还是自己 然后腾空而去
But she made it all about her and she took off.
我是说 去年我被变形者侵犯
I mean, last year, I got bad-touched by a shape-shifter,
可她还是千方百计地只想着自己
and she still found a way to make it about her.
她有时候真是个自私的贱人
She can be such a fucking bitch.
天哪 对不起 我…没想说这么刻薄的话
Jesus, sorry, I-I didn't mean for that to come out so harsh.
该死的
Fucking hell.
这他妈的是怎么回事
Fuck happened here?
这个被五号感染的畜生 吃了餐前点心
Our V'd-up beast enjoyed an amuse-bouche, perhaps?
这就解释了为什么 我们之前没听见动物的动静
Well, explains why we didn't hear no animals.
我十分钟之前就说过这话了
I said that ten minutes ago.
（我们家相信祖国人）
你好 我是凯西
Hi. Kathy.
我一直都想…
I have always wanted...
- 终于见到你了 很开心 - 所以你知道这件事
- It's nice to finally meet you. - So, you knew about this?
知道嘛 很有意思
You know what's funny?
我请你去沃特乐园 肯定请了上百次
I must have asked you, like, a hundred times to go to Voughtland,
但你总说坐过山车会让你恶心
but you always said the roller coasters would make you nauseous.
他这么说的吗 他上去就不想下来呢
He said that? Couldn't get him off that thing.
你妈怎么样
How's your mom?
她还好 她在躲藏 但她还好
She's okay. She's in hiding, but she's okay.
你是警察吗
You're a cop?
- 警官 - 警官
Deputy.
我还以为你在电话公司上班呢
Thought you were working for, um, the telephone company.
你有多久没看见投币电话了
When's the last time you saw a pay phone?
那么 当警察意味着 你在逮捕星光追随者
So, does that mean you're rounding up Starlighters?
你是说恐怖分子吗
You mean terrorists?
- 梅森  - 对不起 我很粗鲁吗
- Mason. -  Sorry, am I being rude?
在我们家客厅
We're all good with
给超人类连环杀手上茶 我们对此都毫无异议吗
serving tea to the Supe serial killer in our living room?
够了
That's enough.
知道吗 我很抱歉
You know what? I'm sorry.
对不起 我来这里 就已经让你们身处险境了
I'm sorry, I've put you guys in danger just by being here.
对我只字不提 你这么做是对的
You were right keeping me a secret.
我走就是了
I'll just go.
安妮 等等
Annie, wait.
我在做酸奶牛肉
I'm making a stroganoff.
是预制菜来的 不过 跟我们一起吃晚餐吧
Well, it's Hamburger Helper, but... Have dinner with us?
去洗洗衣服 洗个澡
Wash your clothes, take a shower.
无意冒犯 不过…你应该洗个澡
No offense, but you could use one.
真是疯了
This is insane.
没搞错吧  午饭又吃门多西诺农场快餐
Really? We're getting fucking Mendo for lunch again?
巴哈绿女神酱蔬菜沙拉 配仿西班牙辣香肠
Baja Green Goddess with Impossible Chorizo.
能不能叫人去趟家得宝
Yeah, can someone make a run to Home Depot
给我买点有机泥炭土  1.4公斤 谢谢
and get me some organic peat moss soil? Three pounds? Thank you.
好了 各位 继续吧
All right, y'all. Let's keep it going.
畅所欲言 什么想法都欢迎
Blue sky day. No bad ideas.
只需要让大家信服 祖国人是我们的救世主
Just got to sell Homelander as our Lord and savior is all.
好吧 这只是个初步的想法
All right, I first thought theater,
不过 他在电视直播上 创造奇迹怎么样
but what if he performed a miracle on live TV?
他可以分开红海之水 将难民送回原籍
He could part the Red Sea and send some refugees back where they came from.
不过 在电视直播上做不到 这些都得用视觉特效做出来
Oh, you couldn't do it live, though. We'd have to VFX the entire thing.
- 对 这里接受大家的各种想法 - 接受这个 你是个白痴
- Right, this is a "yes and" room. - Oh, yes, and you're an idiot.
好吧 不好的版本 是他把水变成葡萄酒
Okay. Uh, the bad version is he turns water into wine.
暂时反过来想一下
Playing a quick game of opposites here, what if...
不做那么恶劣的事情怎么样
it was something not fucking terrible?
要是祖国人飞到世界上 所有的主要圣地
Like, what if Homelander flew into all the major holy sites in the world?
让人们见到新上帝本尊呢
Let the people meet their new god in person, huh?
跟上帝拍自拍
Selfies with God.
为了加强效果 我们可以让他 坐在圣殿山上的一个宝座上
Pitching off of that, we could put him on a throne on the Temple Mount.
用这个景象做海报就行 阿门
That is your poster right there. Amen.
太棒了
This is amazing.
阐明一下 祖国人完全是神
And for the record, Homelander is 100% God,
但难道不会有人觉得他不是吗
um, but won't some people say he's not?
祖国人信仰者会为祖国人教会 带来大笔收入
Uh, a Homelander church would bring in Homelander box office.
我们向上帝祈祷求助 上帝在回应
We prayed to God for help. He's answering.
好像“边炮”说得有道理
Looks like Firecrotch has a point.
- 不好意思 - 没说你
- Excuse me? - The other Firecrotch.
副总统女士
Madam Vice President.
因为根据这项即时民意调查
Because according to the snap poll here,
只有22%的美国人 会接受祖国人做唯一的真神
only 22% of Americans would even accept Homelander as their one true God,
也就是说 让七成的人相信是非常困难的
making a real uphill battle to get him into the 70s,
而他需要七成
which is where he'd need to be.
我得说 你们这些超人类只看重数字
You know, I'd say it's all about numbers with you suits,
不过 沃特加频道从来都不公布数字
but Vought Plus never releases any.
听着 我们需要做的是讲述一个故事
Look, what we need to do is tell a story.
在座的有谁读过 约瑟夫坎贝尔的作品
Who here has read Joseph Campbell?
- 天哪 - 怎么了
-  Jesus Christ. - What?
怪不得《点灯人：正义之光》终结篇
No wonder the Lamplighter: Light of Justice finale
在AV影评网站上得了个劣等评价
got a D-minus on A.V. Club.
好吧 我得保留14个主要人物
Okay, I had to service 14 main characters
给一群《复仇小队》前传的混蛋 做人物交叉
and cross over a bunch of assholes from the Avenging Squad prequel.
那种情况下 谁也写不出好的大结局
You try and make a good finale out of that.
问题是我们在尝试出售一个
The problem is, we are trying to sell
无人想要的产品
a product that no one is asking for.
就像新可乐 对吗  大家都已经爱戴耶稣了
Like New Coke. Right? Everybody already loves Jesus.
恨不得把他拉的屎当作珍馐吃掉
They want to eat right out of his asshole.
当然了 这只是个比喻
Figuratively speaking, of course.
耶稣是一个伟大的人
Jesus was a great man.
- 是的 - 他布道时说的话
- Yeah. -  The things he preached,
让别人打另一边的脸 以及欢迎外来者
turning the other cheek and... taking in foreigners...
关心贫穷之人…
...caring for the poor...
这些东西不再有卖点了
...that shit don't sell no more.
我们需要的是一个 高度赞扬美国人的教会
No, what we need is a church that preaches American.
美国是神的政府 我们美国人是神的选民
America is God's government, and we are his chosen people.
美利坚合众国的昭昭天命 从东海岸到西海岸的广阔领土等等
Manifest Destiny, from sea to shining sea and shit.
而一位真正的 美国英雄是我们的救世主
With a real American hero as our savior.
美国…民主教会
The Democratic Church... of America.
你听到刚才说的数字了
You heard the numbers.
如果我们宣称祖国人是“上帝” 公众不会接受
The public won't accept it if we come out and call Homelander "God."
我知道要称呼他什么
I know what to call him.
- 该死的  - 奥森威尔斯穿着斗篷
Orson Welles wore a cape
是为了盖住自己的大屁股
to cover his fat ass.
剩下的路 我们还是可以飞行的
Well, we could still fly the rest of the way.
我告诉过你了 不许你背我
I told you, you're not fucking carrying me.
好吧
All right.
天哪
Oh, my God.
真是丑八怪
What a couple of uggos.
是什么让你改变了想法
What changed your mind?
昨天你还说不会帮我
Yesterday, you told me you wouldn't help me.
鞭炮说你崇敬我
Firecracker said you looked up to me.
我觉得你也不完全是个白痴
Guess you're not a complete idiot.
我从没说过那种话
I never said that.
你到底想不想让我帮忙
You want my help or not?
那天看你听到 克拉拉沃特名字时的表情
The other day, when Clara Vought's name came up,
我觉得你认识她
I got the impression you knew her.
我跟她打过一两次炮 仅此而已
I fucked her once or twice. That's all.
- 怎么了  - 真的假的
- What? - You did?
那…看来我们就不仅是父子了
Uh... Then, uh, I guess we're related in more ways than one.
她在哪里
Where is she?
死了 自杀
Dead. Suicide.
胡诌八扯 她才不会自杀
Horseshit. She'd never off herself.
可她就是自杀了
Yeah, well, she did.
你看见尸体了吗
Did you see a body?
有发现
Hey. I found something.
蓝图
Blueprints.
是的 走廊像迷宫 地下也有房间
Yeah, there's a labyrinth of hallways and rooms underground.
有个实验室 如果一代五号在这里 那就应该在实验室里
There's the lab. If the V1 is here, that's where it should be.
蓝图 太妙了
Blueprints? Oh, fucking magic.
如果一代五号在这里 那就应该在实验室里
If the V1's here, it ought to be in the lab.
这话我刚说过 你到底会不会听我说话
I just said that. Are you ever gonna fucking listen to me?
亲爱的 你一说值得听的 我就会听的
Yeah, as soon as you say something worth listening to, luv.
你为什么非得这么混蛋
Why do you have to be such an asshole?
你现在终于明白了 不是吗
Oh, finally twigged now, have you?
不 你每天都提醒我
No, you remind me every day.
真是模范父亲 居然让莱恩替你冲锋陷阵
Oh, real Father of the Year, getting Ryan to fight your battles for you.
你把你爸变成僵尸 然后杀了他 居然好意思来说我
Says the twat who turned his dad into a fucking zombie and then killed him.
知道吗 你不仅利用莱恩
Okay, you know what? It's not just Ryan.
- 看看你是怎么对待MM的 - 他怎么对待我了
- Look what you did to M.M. - The fuck did he do to me?
他逼着你下水 害你成了现在这样
He dragged you down in the shit with him, and the worst part,
最糟糕的是什么呢  你允许他这样做 你个软蛋
you let him do it, you fucking pussy.
各位 拜托
Everyone, s'il vous pla?t.
-“软蛋”  - 这里不对劲
-  "Pussy"? - Something is wrong here.
这个亵童犯居然叫你软蛋
This fucking nonce just called you a pussy.
你要饶了他吗
You gonna let him get away with that?
要我干死你吗
Want me to put you in the fucking dirt?
快动手吧 M 来吧 快动手吧
Yeah, fucking do it, M. Do it. Fucking do it.
嘿 够了
Hey. That's enough.
你们都不听我的
None of you ever listen to me.
我听你的
I listen to you.
我一跟别人说话 你就妒火中烧
You get jealous whenever I talk to anyone else.
我不再需要你帮我翻译了
I don't need you to translate for me anymore.
我不是你的小宠物
I'm not your fucking pet.
但你是个小哑巴的时候 他更喜欢你
Nah, but he liked you better when you were a dumb animal.
停下来
Hey, stop!
你们难道看不出来吗  这个地方很奇怪
Can you not see there is something strange about this place?
我们需要集中注意力 一代五号
We need to focus. V1. Huh?
梅森
Mason!
替他抱歉 他…
Sorry about him. He's...
没事 我也经历过这个年龄
It's okay. I used to be his age.
我看见房前的牌子了
I saw the sign out front.
“我们家相信祖国人”
"In this house, we believe in Homelander"?
部门的新主管逼大家 放上这样的牌子
New boss at the department made everybody put 'em up.
我们现在的上司是个 叫“活电线”的超人类
We answer to a Supe named Livewire now.
顺便说一句 我不逮捕星光追随者
I don't round up Starlighters, by the way.
一有这样的命令 我就说自己得了流感
When that order comes in, I catch the flu.
那其他的警官呢
And the other deputies?
他们觉得星光追随者 会劫走他们的孩子
They think that Starlighters are coming for their kids.
但那是沃特宣传的谎言
But that's a lie that Vought sells.
- 我知道 - 那你怎么什么都不说
- I know that. - Then why don't you say anything?
上一个大胆发声的人 在半夜不见了踪影
The last guy that spoke up disappeared,
妻子和孩子们也是
middle of the night, with his wife and kids.
我并不为自己的沉默感到骄傲 安妮 不过 我要保护家人
I'm not proud of it, Annie, but I have a family to protect.
我来这里是想 得到一些答案 做些了结
I came here to get, you know, some answers
不然就来不及了 不过…
and some closure before time runs out, but...
跟你预想的不一样
Not what you expected?
可以这么说
You could say that.
你离开之后 我对自己说
After you left, I told myself that,
你知道的 你就是…你不想要孩子
you know, you just... you didn't want kids,
但也许你就是不想要我
but maybe you just didn't want me.
坐吧
Have a seat.
（星光在沃特闪耀 小女英雄选美大赛）
（星光救了得梅因一家 导致停电）
（星光全介绍）
（《超级七人队新纪元》）
这部电影很烂
This movie was shit.
我确实考虑让你退我钱来着
I did consider asking you for my money back.
我不总是喜欢你的选择
I didn't always approve of the choices you made,
但我一直都为你感到骄傲
but I was always proud of you.
也许在你退出超级七人队时更加骄傲
Maybe even more proud when you quit.
你为什么离开
Why did you leave?
跟你妈初遇时 我正在萨尔瓦多执行传教的任务
The first time I saw your mother was on a church mission. El Salvador.
我们那时很年轻
We were young.
想要拯救世界
Wanted to save the world.
有了你 我们很幸福
We were so happy when you came along.
你妈很确定给你注射五号
And your mom was dead certain that giving you V was...
会给你更美好的生活
gonna give you a better life.
比投币电话修理员…能给你的生活强
Better than a pay phone repairman could give you.
她对我说：“你知道我们如何 才能真正改变世界吗
She asked me, "Do you know how we can really change the world?
答案就是养育超级英雄”
Raise a superhero."
所以你当时同意了
So, you-you got on board?
直到后来她开始告诉你 你是上帝的选民
Until she started telling you you were chosen by God.
问题是 你相信她的话
And th-the thing is, you believed it.
然后 她相信这些话 而我…
And then she believed it, and I just...
我无法继续对你说谎 于是我就离开了
I couldn't keep lying to you, so I left.
- 你甚至都没跟我联系 - 联系你做什么呢
- You never even reached out. - To do what?
粉碎你的梦想 继续对你说谎
Shatter your dreams? Keep lying to you?
怎样都行
I'd have taken either.
我当时是需要你的
I needed you.
如果我能回到过去 做出改变 我会的
If I could go back and change things, I would.
我应该陪在你身边 为你挺身而出
I should have been there for you. Should have stood up for you.
我离开了 我很抱歉 安妮
I'm sorry I left, Annie.
我想我们家人就这样
It runs in the family, I guess.
- 什么意思  - 我那天情绪失控了
- What do you mean? - I flipped out the other day,
我抛下了一个自己很爱的人
and I ditched someone I really love.
他就像…我全心全意地爱着他
It's like he's, um... it's like he's my heart walking on the outside,
- 如果他们伤害他 我就无法… - 嘿 安妮
- and if they got to him, I couldn't-- - Annie.
我们爱的人不是弱点
The people we love aren't a weakness.
他们是我们奋战的原因
They're the reason that we fight.
- 我跟他谈谈可以吗  - 当然
- Hey, is it all right if I talk to him? - Of course.
不过…先敲门
Uh, j-just... knock first.
这是我好不容易学到的教训
I learned that lesson the hard way.
好 实验室在这边
Yeah. The lab is this way.
真他妈的
Fucking hell.
尸体在这里很长时间了 不是吗
They've been here a minute, haven't they?
几十年了
Decades.
猎人 看他们的刀
Hunters. Look at their knives.
这些人互相残杀
These men, they killed each other.
如果这里确实有怪物
What if there is a monster here
但就是我们自己呢
but it's us?
法兰奇 你在胡说些什么
What the fuck are you on about, Frenchie?
弓形虫病
Toxoplasmosis.
这是一种猫屎里的寄生虫 能感染人类
It's a parasite in cat shit. It can infect humans.
它会引起人类暴怒的反应
Makes them react with explosive anger.
你以为我们吃猫屎吗
You think we ate cat shit?
吃 不
Ate? No.
如果一代五号渗入地下水 它就可能使植物发生突变
If the V1 spilled into the groundwater, it could mutate th-the plants.
它们的孢子令我们满心愤怒
Their spores fills us with rage,
我们互相谋杀 然后 一下子…
we murder each other, and voilà...
我们成了这些藤蔓的食物
...we're plant food for these vines.
所以就像《最后生还者》
Okay, so like The Last of Us?
不 那部剧就是《行尸走肉》加蘑菇
No, that is just The Walking Dead with mushrooms.
死掉的露营者 动物 这些猎人
The dead campers, the animals, these hunters.
当然 你们都看见 自己的行为多么怪异了
Surely, you all see how strangely you've been acting.
我们怪异  我可没少看见你吸完可卡因的怪样
Us? I've seen you blow cocaine up your dick hole.
等等 你说得有道理
Wait. You have a point.
几十年来 我大量使用毒品
The copious amount of drugs I've taken for decades
肯定改变了我大脑的运作机制
has surely altered my brain chemistry.
所以我才没受影响
That's why I'm not affected.
看来做瘾君子总算是有点好处了
Guess being a junkie was good for something after all.
罗密欧和朱丽叶
Romeo and fucking Juliet.
你们俩在这场战争中幸存下来 顶多相处六个月就会分开
You two survive this war, I give you six months, tops.
真他妈的
Well fucking well.
我们走
Let's fucking go.
你们要去哪
Wh-Wh... Wh-Where are you going?
- 去干掉那些傻屌 - 你们会害死我们的 蠢货
- To top those cunts. - You'll get us killed, you fucking idiots.
听着 你们现在脑子都不清楚
Neither of you are thinking straight.
法兰奇 别用枪指着我
Get that fucking gun out of my face, Frenchie.
小子 那玩意儿对付不了我
That ain't gonna do shit to me, sonny.
是没用 但我会对付你
No, but I will.
祖国人和士兵男孩杀你们 然后再杀我们
Homelander and Soldier Boy kill you, then kill us.
那样的话 如果这里有一代五号 就会落入祖国人手中
Then, if there's any V1 here, it's Homelander's.
这样你的家人会安全吗
Does that make your family safe?
这是你追求的复仇吗
Is that the revenge you seek?
这会为贝嘉寻得正义吗
Does that make things right for Becca?
好吧
Fine.
趁我们还没互相残杀 或被那两个超人类杀掉
We must hurry before we tear each other apart.
得赶快行动
Or the Supes do.
那计划是什么
So, what's the plan? God!
- 天哪  - 搞什么 法兰奇
- Ugh! - The fuck, Frenchie?
这是鹿尿 猎人用它吸引猎物
It's deer urine. Hunters use it to attract prey,
但我们会用它掩盖气味 不让祖国人闻到我们
but we will use it to hide our scent from Homelander.
你要是敢往我身上喷那玩意儿 我就他妈的把你脑袋揪掉
You spray that shit on me, and I'll rip your fucking head off.
我可不会靠鹿尿救我们的命
I ain't counting on no goddamn deer piss to save our asses.
这是科学嘛 兄弟
It's just science, bro.
射精时 你的身体会损失阳气
When you jizz, masculine vitality leaves your body.
这么重要的东西 得留在体内 对吗 玄色
Got to hold that shit in, right, Noir?
对吗 玄色
Right, Noir?
去…你妈的
Fu-fu-fu-fuck you.
看来你按错了按钮 小兄弟
Looks like you hit the wrong button there, broseph.
贱…贱人说什么
B-B-Bitch says what?
什么
What?
干什么
我只想谈谈
I just want to talk.
哇
Wow.
上面没有你的照片
Your picture was never up there.
很好
Yeah, good.
（采婷保湿乳）
很好 我是说 那样挺好
Good. I mean, uh, yeah, no, that's good.
我的墙上不挂叛徒的照片
I don't put traitors on my wall.
知道吧
Okay, you know...
他们说我的那些事 都不是真的
what they say about me, none of it's true.
你说的是靠给人吹箫进入超级七人队
Do you mean the part that you blew your way into The Seven
还是你是贩运儿童的恐怖分子
or that you're a terrorist who traffics children?
所以你是肯定 不会进我货车的后车厢了
So that's, like, a hard no on getting into the back of my van?
嘿 听着 梅森
Hey, look, Mason,
你每天去祖国人学院上学
you go to school at Homelander Academy
回家刷几千条抖音视频
and you come home and you watch thousands of TikToks every day.
事实怎么能 跟你接触的虚假信息竞争
How is the truth supposed to compete with that?
无所谓了 你是联调局的头号通缉犯
Whatever. You're, like, the FBI's Most Wanted.
不管你喜欢与否 联调局的头号通缉犯是你姐
Oh, okay. Well, like it or not, the FBI's Most Wanted is your sister,
对此 你可以继续表现得像个混蛋 或者 我们可以谈谈
so you can keep being an asshole about it or, you know, we can also talk about it.
有第三个选项吗
Is there a third option?
（邓肯）
让我猜猜 巧克力奶油馅 每周四早上 对吗
Let me guess. Chocolate cream-filled every Thursday morning, right?
以前 上学前 我爸会带我去买
Dad used to take me before school.
其实 那是我最想念的事情之一
It's one of the things I miss the most, actually.
我以为他用我来伪装身份
I think he was just taking me as his beard.
我觉得他想让我得糖尿病
Yeah, I feel like he's giving me diabetes.
不在这里
Okay, it's not here.
去他妈的 去你妈的 真他妈的
Fuck this and fuck you and fuck me.
这就是在浪费时间
This is a goddam waste of time.
布彻尔 看看
Butcher. Take a look.
也许某人先于我们找到了它
Maybe some motherfucker beat us to it.
就在不久之前
Not too long ago, neither.
他们一拳就砸开了保险箱 那上面可是积累了80年的铁锈
They punched 80 years of rust right off the safe.
据我们所知 有几个超人类有那么大的力气
Now, how many Supes do we know that can punch this hard?
12个 也许更多
A dozen. Maybe more.
那是什么
What is it?
- 海洛因 - 海洛因
- Heroin. -  Heroin.
你他妈的当然识别得出来
Of course you would fucking know that.
拳头力大无穷
So a punch like a bleeding sledgehammer
对海洛因上瘾
and a taste for fucking smack.
炸弹视野
Bombsight.
几十年都没人见过炸弹视野了 他很有可能已经死了
No one has seen Bombsight for decades. He's likely dead.
要是他没死呢 混蛋
What if he's not, asshole?
也就他有可能知道一代五号在这里
He'd be about the only other cunt that would know this shit was here.
你说的是士兵男孩 第一支队伍里的炸弹视野
You mean Bombsight from Soldier Boy's first team?
他体内不是已经有一代五号了吗  为什么还需要更多
Wouldn't he have already been shot up with V1? What's he need more for?
你好 艾德 没什么事吧
Hey, Ed. Everything all right?
很抱歉 在你的休息日打扰你
Yeah, I'm sorry to bother you on your day off.
真不敢相信我会这样问 星光在你家吗
This is gonna sound crazy. Is Starlight in there?
我…抱歉 什么
I'm s... I'm sorry, what?
我接到了梅森的电话
I got a call from Mason.
但这是个玩笑 对吗  告诉我这是个玩笑
But it's a joke, right? Tell me it's a joke.
- 她是我女儿 - 你女儿
- She's my daughter. - Your daughter?
天哪 爸 说谎都不会
Jesus Christ. Can't he ever fucking lie?
我都认识你20年了 你从没…
I've known you 20 years, and y-you never--
我本应该告诉你的
I should have told you.
- 她是个连环杀手 - 她不是 我向你保证
- She's a serial killer. - She's not. I promise you.
我求你了 回到警车上去 别管这事了
I'm begging you, get back in your cruiser and let this go.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
我才不会因为这事死在拘留营里 我得把她抓起来
I am not dying in a prison camp over this. I got to take her in.
你得让开
You need to step aside right now.
拜托 艾德 放松点
Please, Ed, just take a breath.
- 立刻举起双手 - 我看不行
- Hands up right now. -  I don't think so.
走开
Walk away.
- 艾德 放下… - 我说了 立刻
- Ed, put it down. - I said now.
走开
Walk away.
- 不 你被捕了 - 艾德 放松
- No. You're under arrest. -  Ed, relax.
各位 拜托…
Everybody, please, just--
- 我警告你 - 我说了 走开
-  I'm warning you. - I said walk away.
你们俩都住手
Would the both of you fucking stop!
我…很抱歉 我就是…
I-I'm sorry, I just...
艾德 我们每周日在教堂里都挨着坐
Ed, we sit next to each other in church every Sunday.
帕姆死后 你在这里吃了多少个月的晚饭
After Pam died, you ate dinner here for how many months?
没错 可你却一直都 当着我的面说谎
Yeah, and you lied to my face the whole time.
我知道你害怕 我也害怕
I know you're scared. I'm scared, too.
但一直以来沃特逼我们做的事
But what Vought's been making us do,
到别人家里抓捕 逮捕我们的邻居 把他们送去…
pulling people out of their homes, our neighbors, and sending them to...
天知道送去了哪里 你知道这样做是不对的
God knows where. You know it's wrong.
安妮是我的女儿 我爱她
Annie's my daughter, and I love her.
我很久之前就应该为她挺身而出
I should've stood up for her a long time ago.
她并不是他们说的那个样子 她是个好人 艾德
She's not what they say she is. She's a good person, Ed.
如果好人停止努力做正确的事
And if good people stop trying to do the right thing,
那我们还有什么机会
then what the hell chance do we have?
她最好在一个小时内离开
She better be gone in an hour,
否则 我对天发誓 我会带着活电线回到这里
or I swear to God, I'm coming back with Livewire,
我会把你们俩都抓起来
I'm hauling you both in.
谢谢 谢谢你
Thanks. Thank you.
一股鹿尿味儿
Smells like deer piss.
知道嘛 上次我在这里时刚下前线
The last time I was here, I was fresh off the front lines,
头发里还粘着纳粹的脑浆呢
still picking Nazi brains out of my hair.
只有出类拔萃的士兵 才会入选参加沃特博士的试验
And only the best of the best got selected for Dr. Vought's trials.
同性恋软蛋是绝对不会入选的
Not soft little hog chompers.
当然 我忘记你有多么强悍了
Of course. No, I forgot how tough you were.
我不是不打炮的怪胎
Hey, I'm not the weirdo who doesn't fuck.
我是说 你的老二跟你的斗篷一样没用
I mean, your cock's as useless as your cape.
要是不把老二放进小穴里沾湿 那成名还有什么用
What's the point of being famous if you're not getting your dick wet?
我的老二从风暴的小穴里 拔出来时湿漉漉的
Oh, oh, my dick was sopping wet
还在她的脸蛋上擦干呢
when I pulled it out of Stormfront and wiped it on her fucking chin.
看 更多丑八怪
Ooh, look. More uggos.
是你的朋友吧
Friends of yours?
该死
Oh, shit.
（警告 探测到移动）
- 他们就在上面 - 我们最好赶快走人
- They're right above us. - We best get the fuck out of here.
- 快点 - 等等 不找一代五号了吗
- Come on. - Hey. Hey. What about the V1?
要是一代五号在炸弹视野手上
If Bombsight has the V1,
那我们就不用毁掉它了
then it saves us from having to torch it.
你在说些什么
What are you talking about?
“我们”指谁
Who's "us"?
怎么 你觉得这个世界需要更多 长生不老的超人类傻屌吗
What? You think the world needs more immortal cunts, do you?
我们需要它来救安妮和喜美子
We need it to save Annie and Kimiko.
你一直都在计划这事 不是吗
You've been planning this this whole time, haven't you?
祖国人会听到我们说话的
Shh. Homelander will hear us.
而你 你又委曲求全地帮他达到目的
And you, you've just been going along with it again.
我们不能冒这个风险 休伊
We can't take the risk, Hughie.
如果她不得不成为附带伤害
And if she has to be collateral damage so that
好让祖国人死掉 我女儿活下去
Homelander dies and my daughter lives,
那我们就别无选择
we ain't got no fucking choice.
你说得轻巧 病毒又杀不死你
Oh, easy for you to say. It won't fucking kill you.
但至少他知道什么时候闭上嘴
Well, at least he knows when to keep his gob shut
并且执行命令
and do as he's fucking told.
你说什么
Excuse me?
不 我们没时间争执 我们得马上就找到出去的路
No, no, no. We don't have time for this. We need to find a way out now.
想知道个小秘密吗 布彻尔
Want to know a little secret, Butcher?
得知你快死的时候 我心里高兴着呢
I cheered when I found out that you were dying,
因为至少我们终于 不用再忍受你那惨兮兮的模样了
'cause at least we'd finally be done with your miserable ass.
我以前总对他们说：“别放弃布彻尔
You know, I used to say to these guys, "Don't give up on Butcher.
他内心有善良的一面 只是表现出来很难” 我是错的
There's good in him fighting to get out." I was wrong.
要是你内心还有人性 也已经消逝了
If there was anything human in there, it's dead.
你的胸膛里只有八爪鱼一般的 老二藤蔓 你就是个怪物
Underneath that chestful of octo-cocks, you are just a fucking monster.
也许我更喜欢这个样子
Well, maybe I like it better that way.
那个寄生虫不仅在你体内 你就是寄生虫
That parasite's not just in you. It is you.
- 你就是癌症 - 小点声
- You're the cancer. - Lower your voices.
你跟祖国人一样坏 也许更坏
You are just as bad as Homelander, maybe worse.
我不容许你害我们跟你一起玩完
And I'm not gonna let you drag us all down with you.
- 你又能怎样呢 小子  - 我要杀了你
- And what you gonna do about it? - I'll fucking kill you.
不 小心
No, stop!
喜美子
Kimiko!
请冷静
Please. Calm down.
我说过了 我不是你的小宠物
I told you I'm not your pet.
我受够听你指挥了
I'm done following your commands.
喜美子
Kimiko.
动手吧 MM
Come on, M.M.
我是说 要是布彻尔允许的话
I mean, if Butcher will let you.
各位 请住手
Everybody, please stop!
喂 你这是要去哪呀
Oi! Where do you think you're going?
嘿
Mon coeur. Hey.
别…
Don't.
强悍个狗屁
Tough guy, my ass.
- 什么  - 你 你的那一套
- What? - You, your whole bit.
勇气和荣誉那一套
This whole "guts and glory" thing.
一派胡言 真是个笑话
What a fucking joke.
我读过你的机密文档
I read your classified file.
你哥在登陆安齐奥时作战英勇 获得了银星勋章
Your brother won a Silver Star for bravery at Anzio,
因此 你恳求父亲靠贿赂 为你争取到参加沃特博士试验的机会
and that's what made you beg your father to buy you a spot in Dr. Vought's trials.
因为看见哥哥独自享有所有的荣耀 让你难受得要死
Because it killed you to see your brother dripping in all that glory,
让你相形之下更显得软弱无能
making you look all the more feeble in comparison.
关于我 你一无所知
You don't know shit about me.
真的吗
Really?
我知道他们想给你注射五号时
I know that when they tried to inject you with the V,
你吓得要死 他们只好把你绑在床上
you were so fucking petrified that they had to strap you to the table.
你都吓尿了 大声叫妈
And you pissed yourself, crying for your mommy
像个爱发牢骚 被宠坏的富家子弟 那就是你的本来面目
like the whiny, spoiled little rich boy that you are.
你的父母给了你一切 可你根本不值一文
They gave you the world, and you, you deserve nothing.
天哪 这是什么鬼地方
Oh, Christ. What's this shithole now?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
干得漂亮
Oh, well done.
我30秒之内就会出去
I'll be out of here in 30 seconds.
也许出不来
Maybe. Maybe not.
是浓缩铀
It's enriched uranium.
他们会把超人类关进里面 看我们能否在原子弹爆炸后存活下来
They'd stick us Supes in there to see if we could survive an atomic bomb.
普通人几分钟内就会死掉
Now, for a normal joe, they'd be dead in minutes,
不过对你来说 那就跟胃肠炎差不多
but for you, it's a stomach flu.
不过 祝你好运
Good luck, though,
一边要从防超人类舱里出来 一边大量流血
getting out of a Supe-proof cell while you're bleeding out of your ass.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
我要毁掉找到的任何一代五号 你个爱操男人的软蛋
I'm gonna go destroy any V1 that I find, you Triple Crown cock jockey.
- 为什么  - 你不明白是吗
- Why? - You don't get it, do you?
你不明白我有多受不了你
How much I can't fucking stand you.
休伊
Hughie.
来吧 小子 来试试身手
Come on, son. Come and have a go.
要是全世界现在 能看见你的样子就好了
Oh, if only the world could see you now.
没有什么“超人之处”是吧
Not so fucking super, are you?
你…脸上有点…
You, uh... you got a bit of...
你爸惩罚你了吗
Did your dad put you in time-out?
肯定很心痛吧
That's got to sting,
知道他宁愿独自一人度过永生
knowing he'd rather spend eternity all alone
也不要你陪着他
than with the likes of you.
怎么了 舌头被操断了
What's the matter? Cunt got your tongue?
奇观真是层出不穷啊
Will wonders ever cease?
告诉我
Tell me something.
要是真的注射了一代五号 你觉得自己就成神了 是吗
If you do get the juice in you, you think that makes you a god, don't you?
看来我还是很了解你的
Seems like I know you pretty well after all.
正因为如此 我知道即使有几十亿的傻瓜
Which is why I know that even if you had a billion twats
对你阿谀奉承 为你大唱赞歌
gargling your bollocks and singing hosanna,
你还是不会开心
you still wouldn't be happy.
因为内心深处 你就是个 懦弱 敏感 渴求被爱的小男孩
'Cause deep down, you're just a weak, thin-skinned, needy little boy.
听说你把自己的儿子打了个半死
You beat the shit out of your own son.
最懦弱的也不过于此吧
Don't get weaker than that.
莱恩活着是因为他很强大
Ryan is alive. Because he's strong.
因为他是我儿子 真神之子
'Cause he's my son. The son of God.
你才不是什么神
You ain't no god.
不如我去拿病毒
How's about I go fetch the virus, and then we'll watch you
然后我们看着你痛苦地死掉吧
shit your fucking spine out?
没在你手上对吧
You don't have it, do you?
你没病毒
The virus.
- 是吗  - 对 你没有病毒
- Don't I? - No, you don't.
不然你早就用了
You would have used it by now.
你没有办法阻止我 不是吗
You have no way to stop me, do you?
威廉姆 你不知道 自己要对付的是什么
Oh, William. You have no idea what you're up against.
你无法干预
You can't intervene.
我会得到一代五号 那时
I will get the V1, and when I do,
我要将你活活折磨死
I'm gonna flay you alive.
你 星光 所有不信仰我的人…
You, Starlight, all the nonbelievers.
你们都会淹死在自己的血海之中
You're all gonna fucking drown in your own blood.
我向你保证 我死之前
I promise you, before I die...
一定会击败你
...I'll fucking have you.
你们都死定了
You're all fucking paste!
我能得到应许于我的
I can take what's mine,
这个世界 我生来就拥有它
and that makes this whole fucking shit ball my birthright!
是我命中注定的
My destiny!
混蛋
Fucker!
该死 妈的
Shit. Damn.
他妈的
Shit. Shit.
该死
Fuck.
搞什么
The fu...
喂
Hey!
我的天哪
My God.
奎恩
Quinn.
你认识这个男人
You knew this man?
你们一起参加了沃特博士的试验
You were in Dr. Vought's trials together.
估计就是你
Figures this would be you.
你个丑八怪混蛋
You ugly piece of shit.
你之前恨我来着
Oh, you hated me.
我只是个富有 有权势的混蛋
Yeah, I was just a rich, entitled asshole.
从没见过哪怕一次真正的搏斗
Never seen a lick of real combat, huh?
你还他妈的恨我 不是吗
You still fucking hate me, don't you?
这个生物心里只有憎恨
This creature is nothing but hate.
让我们憎恨
He makes us hate.
是他造成了这一切
He's the cause of all of this.
听我说
Listen to me.
只有你才能了结这一切 了结他的痛苦吧
You are the only one who can end it. Put a stop to his misery.
了结他的痛苦 不 那可不行
Put him out of his misery? No, no. God, no.
不 我喜欢他这个样子
No, I like him like this.
去你妈的 贱人
Oh, fuck you, bitch!
我不值得我所拥有的东西吗
Oh, I didn't deserve what I got, huh?
去你妈的
Fuck you. Fuck you!
我风范不减当年 所以去你妈的
'Cause I still got it.
我一如既往地强大  我他妈的比你强
I got all of it. I fucking won!
要是你不杀了他 我们都会死的
If you won't kill him, all of us will die.
我知道奎因为什么恨你
I know why Quinn hates you.
是吗
Oh, is that right?
因为他看到你的真面目
Because he sees you for what you really are.
他曾是真正的士兵
He was a real soldier.
而你只是个穿着制服装装样子的男孩
You were just a boy playing dress-up.
不过你成了英雄 他却只能这样活着
But you got to be the hero while he got to be this.
真是毫无公正可言
Now, where's the justice in that?
你在那上面才对
- It should be you up there. - Shut up.
- 闭嘴 - 这都应该是你的痛苦才对
It should be your pain.
你不过就是个懦夫
You are nothing but a coward.
我让你闭嘴
I said shut your fucking mouth!
休伊
Hughie?
我…我很抱歉
I'm-I'm sorry.
没事
Yeah.
我也很抱歉
Me, too.
妈的 对不起
Fuck. I'm sorry.
我太抱歉了
I'm so fucking sorry.
这是我吃过的最好吃的酸奶牛肉了
Well... That was the best stroganoff I have ever had.
肯定不是 不过感谢你的好心夸奖
It definitely wasn't, but that's kind of you.
你想说什么吗
You have something you want to say?
对不起
Sorry.
- 你想再说一次吗  - 我很抱歉
- You want to try that again? - I'm sorry.
很好 不过你20岁之前都被禁足了
Good. But you're grounded till you're 20.
禁足到30岁还差不多
Mm, more like 30.
我希望我们会再见
I hope we see each other again.
我也是
Me, too.
安妮 别犯我犯过的错误
Annie? Don't make the same mistake I did.
别放弃自己爱的人 好吗
Don't give up on the people you love, all right?
一代五号不在这里
The V1 wasn't here.
你…
Were you...
你在哭吗
Were you crying?
快下手吧
Just fucking do it already.
谢谢
Thank you.
要不是你挺身而出 我们是出不来的
We wouldn't have made it out if you hadn't stepped up.
知道嘛 负责…
Yeah, well, taking charge...
是我做过的最糟糕的事
...was the most horrible thing I've ever done.
永远都别再让我负责了
Never let me do it again. Never.
对不起 我叫你瘾君子软蛋来着
I'm sorry I called you a feckless junkie man-whore.
我没记得你这样说我
I don't remember you calling me that.
没有吗 我还以为我说了呢
I didn't? I thought I did.
你没说错 我以前确实是
You're not wrong. I was, once.
不过 我现在戒掉了 你让我变成什么样我都做得到
But I am clean now. And I can be whatever you need.
我不想改变你
I don't want to change you.
是…
It's that...
我在努力改变自己
...I'm trying to change myself.
我现在能说话了是因为…
The reason I can speak now, it's...
是因为我很努力地卸掉情感上的包袱
it's because I did so much work to let go of my... chaos.
可你热爱情感上的包袱
The thing is... you love chaos.
你擅长应对它们 这倒没关系 不过
You thrive in it. Which is fine, but...
我不能把那些包袱再扛起来了
...I can't go back to that.
那我们之间算什么
So, where does that leave us?
对不起 我不应该离开你的 我应该待在这里的
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have left you. I should've been here.
其实 我很开心你不在 错过今天是件大好事
Actually, I'm so, so glad you weren't. Super good day to miss.
听着 伙计 我之前说的那些鬼话…
Listen, mate. That shite I said...
嘿 别告诉我那不是真心话 好吗
Hey. Don't tell me you didn't mean it, a'ight?
因为我说的每个字都是发自内心的
'Cause I sure as hell meant every fucking word I said.
那我们之间有问题了
So, we got a problem?
没有 伙计 没有
We cool, man. We cool.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
思考
Just thinking.
“好戏”要开场了
Well, the shit show is on.
从东海岸
? From sea ?
（神父大人即将宣布“重大消息”）
到西海岸
? to shining sea ?
美国
? America ?
是的
Yes! Yes!
兄弟姐妹们
Brothers and sisters.
兄弟姐妹们 我们今日得以见证
Brothers and sisters, we are truly, truly fortunate
实在是万幸之事
to bear witness on this day.
因为今天是撒马利亚人怀抱 史上最伟大的一天
Because today... is the greatest day in the history of Samaritan's Embrace.
- 能给我一句阿门吗  - 阿门
- Can I get an amen? -  Amen!
- 我爱这种场面 很爱 - 250年前…
I mean, I love all this, love,
难道你不相信耶稣什么的吗
but don't you believe in Jesus or whatever?
我信过 现在我信的是祖国人
I did. Now I believe in Homelander.
她在说谎
She's lying.
- 可不是嘛 - 什么
- No shit. - Excuse me?
不过今天 兄弟姐妹们 今天
But today, brothers and sisters, today,
我们让美国重回正轨
we set America back on its true course.
从今天开始
Starting today,
兄弟姐妹们 我们致力于 一项神圣的重塑之伟业
brothers and sisters, we commit ourselves to a divine rebranding.
我们将成为有信仰的爱国者
We will be patriots of faith.
我们将实现国父们的梦想
We will fulfill our Founding Fathers' dream.
- 我们会的  - 就在今天
Today,
从今天开始 撒玛利亚人怀抱变为
starting today, Samaritan's Embrace becomes
美国民主教会
the Democratic Church of America.
现在来分享 他对我们新教会的神圣计划…
And here, to share his holy plan for our new church,
他不只是个男人
he is not just a man...
他不只是个超人类
...he's not just a super man...
他是我主的先知
...he is the Prophet of the Lord!
他是美国的先知
He is the Prophet of America!
他就是先知祖国人
He is the Prophet Homelander!
祖国人…
Homelander! Home--
（根据炸药娱乐漫画系列改编 创作 加思恩尼斯）
（绘制 达里克罗伯逊）
字幕翻译：张扬
创意监督 肖雪